Just because he's been married
doesn't mean he only likes women.
Wait...
We're out in public.
I worked so hard just to see you.
Don't I deserve a reward?
(Sometimes I wonder
if I really deserve this.)
I thought I'd never fall in love again
for the rest of my life.
And that I'd just die all alone.
But then I met you.
If you're lonely, I'm here for you.
Whether it's nursing care or whatever, I'll
take care of you for the rest of your life.
I'll do everything I can
to help you live a long, healthy life.
Good morning, Ai-chan.
Good morning.
Hold on.
Making me blush first thing in the morning.
Stop it.
Sorry, sorry.
Am I being a little too naughty?
More than just a little.
(Actually, since this spring,
this older guy)
(is my boss,
the president of my company.)
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 4)
Hello, this is Apis Corporation.
(That being said...)
Please hold on a moment.
(Even though we're in the same company,
I barely get to see Okumi-san.)
You're stuttering quite a bit.
I bit my tongue.
Please transfer to line three.
Hello.
A huge batch of copy paper just arrived.
Who ordered it?
It's not two packs.
It's twenty.
I did.
Well, it won't go bad anyway.
Just be more careful next time.
I'm sorry.
Is this package for the president?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Sorry.
Could someone help deliver this?
Is your new guy free?
Yes, he's free.
- Hizaki.
- Yes.
You know where the boardroom is, right?
Could you take this over there?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Ai-chan~
You never come to see me.
How could I just drop by without a reason?
I'm just a rookie, after all.
It'd be weird, right?
A new employee
just casually walking into the boardroom.
Sorry about that.
I guess I'm the only
one getting carried away.
I told you, we're at work.
- Just for a little bit, it's fine, right?
- That's not the point.
Ai-chan.
Keep up the good work.
You too, Okumi-san.
You're Hizaki, right?
Thanks for bringing it over.
Your face is really red. Be careful.
Are there security cameras
in there or something?
I can't even do my job right.
What the hell am I doing?
- GA should've gotten a package for me, can you get it?
- Sure
Send Ai to the boardroom.
You know,
this is my first office romance.
It's great.
You're starting to want happiness
for yourself. Isn't that a good thing?
Alright, next task.
Could you compile this data
into a report for me?
Sure.
Hizaki, how are you holding up?
No problem.
I should be done...
very soon.
Finished.
(A file with the same name already
exists. Replace it?) (Cancel) (Replace)
- Ah!
- Huh?
I accidentally overwrote the file.
Ahh...
It's already noon.
Go take a break.
I'll handle the rest.
Okay.
I'm such a loser.
I'm so tired.
I'll get used to it eventually, but...
when exactly is "eventually"?
Ai-chan.
Today, just focus on
making yourself feel good.
Alright, let's blow off
some steam before bed...!
It'll help me sleep better.
It feels different from
how Okumi-san does it.
Is Ai-chan here?
Okumi-san!
Sorry for dropping by unannounced.
I heard you were feeling down,
so I got a little worried.
I always mess things up.
I'm completely useless at the company.
Why did they even hire me?
That hurts to hear.
Do you think our HR department
has such terrible judgment?
If you feel sorry,
then make it up to me.
Huh?
Why are only your nipples wet?
That's...
You were playing with yourself.
No, I wasn't.
Really?
Then how did they get like this?
I did touch them, but...
it didn't feel good at all.
Even though...
I was just going to take
one look at you and leave.
I just touched myself.
I'm already soaking wet.
Jeez, where did you learn
how to be such a tease?
Ah.
I can't hold back much longer.
It's okay.
You don't have to hold back.
I'll take care of you.
Okumi-san...
Did he leave?
It hurts.
This sucks.
(Okumi-san)
- Hello.
- Sorry about that.
I'm heading out on a business trip today.
How's your body holding up?
We went a little too hard.
It stings a bit now.
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, um...
What?
Nothing.
Have a safe trip.
I...
can't hold back much longer.
It's okay.
You don't have to hold back.
I'll take care of you.
(He said he'd take care of me.)
(What exactly am I
to Okumi-san?)
(Next Episode)
- Long time no see.
- You even show up for the death
anniversary of someone you didn't love.
I don't want to be cute or protected.
I want to be a man you can rely on.
It's all my fault, after all.
Let me take care of you.